Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Records Documenting Women's Gymnastics
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Department of Athletics, Yale University, records documenting women's gymnastics
1978-1997
RU 1041
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.25
(1 box)
The materialss consist of correspondence, publications and press releases documenting women's gymnastics at Yale.
Yale University. Dept. of Athletics
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 38-B (YRG 38-B), Records documenting specific sports at Yale.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The materials were ransferred from the Department of Athletics, 2005.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of correspondence, publications and press releases documenting women's gymnastics at Yale.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by type of material.
College athletes; College sports; Gymnastics; Women athletes; Women gymnasts; Yale University -- Gymnastics; Yale University -- Sports; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Dept. of Athletics
- Records of the gymnastics team, 1978-1997; Accession 2006-A-116; 0.25
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2025.
  - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Press releases, circa 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Publications, 1981-1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Contest management, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - General, 1982-19890 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ivy League, 1985-1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Post Season, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Post Season, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Post Season, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Gymnastics Association, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)